exports.Questions = { chem101:[
    {
        question:"who is mr Arman Grema Viruse",
        ans:"a programmer",
        decoy:["web developer", "web designer", "electrical engineer","that is madeness to the core indeed"]
    },
    {
        question:"do mr Arman Grema Viruse only develop web",
        ans:"of course not",
        decoy:["of course not", "web designer", "electrical engineer", "that is madeness to the core indeed"]
    },
    {
        question:"Who is the architect of modern Nigeria",
        ans:"Lord lugard",
        decoy:["Lord lugard", "Ahmadu Bello and tafawa balewa", "Nnamdi Azikiwe", "George Tubman"]
    },
    {
        question:"Ethics means.....",
        ans:"Non of the above",
        decoy:["Arretion", "Non of the above","Incantation","All of the above"]
    },
    {
        question:"H Greenberg classify Nigerian languages into phyla",
        ans:"False",
        decoy:["False", "True"]
    },
    {
        question:"There is sahara in the north and tropical in southern",
        ans:"Nigeria",
        decoy:[ "Chad",
             "Nigeria",
             "Niger",
             "Ghana"
            ]
    },
    {
        question:"Christain and islam religions advice....... dressing ",
        ans:"decent",
        decoy:[ "descent", 
             "indescent",
             "decent",
              "indecent"
            ]
    },
    {
        question:"Fulani is a Nilo sahara language ",
        ans:"False",
        decoy:["True",
                "False"
            ]
    },
    {
        question:"Urbanization in Nigeria began in the Year........ ",
        ans:"1861",
        decoy:["1900",
            "1861",
            "1960"
            
            ]
    },
    {
        question:"listed countries to French.. and Nigeria  to America  ",
        ans:"True",
        decoy:["True",
                "False"
            ]
    },
    {
        question:"Language symbols can be spoken, read and written ",
        ans:"True",
        decoy:["True",
                "False"
            ]
    },
    {
        question:"Nigeria was derived from \"Niger area\" ",
        ans:"True",
        decoy:["True",
                "False"
            ]
    },
    {
        question:"The northern and southern protectorates were declared in the year",
        ans:"False",
        decoy:[ "1914",
             "1900",
             "1960",
             "1963"
            
            ]
    },
    {
        question:"Course on right and citizen rights is relevant ",
        ans:"School curriculum",
        decoy:["School curriculum",
            "School syllabus",
            "Societies"
            
            ]
    },
    {
        question:"The main objective of the colonialism is to establish local trade and technology ",
        ans:"True",
        decoy:["True",
                "False"
            ]
    },
    {
        question:"The Berlin Conference was call on taking control of  ",
        ans:"False",
        decoy:["True",
                "False"
            ]
    },
    {
        question:"Fulani is a Nilo sahara language ",
        ans:"Africa",
        decoy:["Africa",
            "Eastern europe",
            "Asia"]
            
    },
    {
        question:"The oil of the south south is in",
        ans:"Niger delta",
        decoy:["Niger basin",
             "Niger delta",
             "Niger/beneu", 
             "Niger Congo"
            
            ]
    },
    {
        question:"Language is defined as ",
        ans:"mutual collection of dialects",
        decoy:[ "traditional culture",
            "mutual collection of dialects",
             "society",
            "cultural system"
            
            ]
    }
]
}
